Kids,on my first day as a college professor,
孩子们 我当大学教授的第一天
there re two things I didn't know that I wish did.
我真希望自己当时知道两件事
The first thing was that your mother was in that classroom.
第一件是 你们的妈妈就在那间教室里
The second thing?
第二件?
Well,to explain tt, we have to go back to the beginning of the summer,
为了解释清楚  我们首先得回到夏天刚开始时
when,after a ye of wrestling with their feelings for each other,
在挣扎犹豫了一年对彼此的感觉后
Barney and Robin finally,well...
Barney和Robin总算是 呃...
Lily,volume. Use your indoor "whoo."
Lily 注意音量 用你室内的欢呼声
Sorry,whoo!
抱歉 唔!
It's jt they kissed! They're finally a couple.
他们接吻了! 他们终于成了一对儿
Oh,my God,you guys! This is our first double date!
噢 天哪 伙计们!  这是我们第一次四人约会!
First of millions! What if our kids get married? Oh,I love this!
无数次中的第一次! 说不定我们的孩子们会结婚? 爱死这个了!
Yeah... Lily,listen.
呃... Lily 听我说
Barney's awesome.
Barney很赞
Ron's more than just awe -"some."
Ronbin不仅仅是很赞
She's awe-"quite a bit." She's awe-"a whole darn lot."
她是无与伦比 她简直是出神入化啊
Wait,what are you saying?
等等 你们在说啥?
We're just not feeling it right now.
我们现在没那种感觉了
- But we'll totally still be friends. - Oh,yeah.
- 但我们还是会继续做朋友 - 对
Is it something I did?
是我做错了什么吗?
- Oh,no,no,no, no,God,no. - No,no,no.
- 噢 不不不 老天 不是你 - 不 不 不
- Lily,it's not you. It'ss. - Yeah. It's us.
- Lily 不是你的错 是我们的问题 - 对 是我们的问题
You understand,right?
你能理解的对吧?
Sure,of course.
当然 当然了
As long as you're happy, I'm happy.
只要你们开心 我就开心
We were gonna takecooking and we were gonna go on camping trips together
我们本来可以一起上烹饪课 一起去露营
and then we were gonna sit around telng funny stories about our cooking lessons and our camping trips.
然后坐在一起 讲我们烹饪课和露营时的笑料
I know,I know.
我明白 我明白
So,has the boat sailed onex tonight or...
那今晚我们就不ooxx了么...
After that,the summer went by way too fast.
在那之后 夏天转瞬即逝
Until all of a sudden, it was the Friday before my firsday as a college professor.
忽然之间 就到了我第一天当教授 之前的那个周五
- Whoa,what's this? - Oh,boy.
- 哇噢 这是什么? - 噢 天哪
It's just a little something that we got for you
只是我们给你买的小玩意
that used to belong to my favorite professor of all time.
曾属于我最喜欢的教授
A fedora.
一顶软呢帽
I'm Indiana Jones! I'm Indiana Jones!
我是印第安纳琼斯! 我是印第安纳琼斯!
That,my friend, is the Dinator 8000,
我的朋友 这个就是"统治者8000"
the best bullwhip on the market, according to my whip guy.
据我的鞭子中介说  这是市面上最好的鞭子
Yeah,I have a whip guy.
是的 我有个鞭子中介
You know what we should do? We should...
知道我们该干嘛吗? 我们应该...
Finish ourrinks,go out in the alley,and whip stuff.
把酒喝掉 去外面的巷子里 用鞭子抽点什么
God,you just get me.
老天 你真了解我
Okay,I should get going. I got a date.
好了 我该走了 我有约会
Oh,are you still seeing that guy?
噢 你还在跟那男人约会吗?
Uh,even better, seeing him naked. What!
呃 更进一步了  跟他裸裎相对了 牛吧!
I should go,too.
我也该走了
I hooked up with this Chinese girl last night, and I don't know,it's weird.
我昨晚跟个中国妞在一起 说不清 挺怪怪的
I already feel like seconds.
我已经迫不及待了
Okay,Ted,you got first whip!
OK Ted 你来抽第一下!
All right.
好
Hey,dummy. What did tell you about smoking in here?
嘿 假人 我不是警告过你 不许在这儿抽烟的么?
Make him whip the habit!
把他那陋习给抽掉!
I'so excited about this whip! I got whip fever!
这一抽搞得我好兴奋!  我染上鞭子高烧了!
Just whip him,Ted! Don't even aim! Just whip him!
赶紧抽他 Ted! 别瞄准! 直接抽!
I am so sorry.
我太抱歉了
No,it's just the whip's not a toy,Ted.
没事 但鞭子不是什么玩具 Ted
There's such a thing as common sense,you know.
这是人人皆知的道理
Hey,you can whip me if you want.
嘿 要是你想的话 可以抽我
I will,some other time.
我会的 下次吧
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品  本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- sync:咔肉肉
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译:阿衡 葱家的小毛毛  校对:葱家的小毛毛 阿衡 时间轴:咔肉肉
How I Met Your Mother Season05 Episode01
老爸老妈罗曼史 第五季第1集
So,how long has this been going on?
你们俩这样多久了?
All summer.
整个夏天
I knew it! I knew it! I knew it!
我就知道! 我就知道! 我就知道!
You guys are boyfriend and girlfriend.
你们俩就是男女朋友
- Wow,no. Whoa,whoa,whoa,Lily. - Girlfriend?
- 哇噢 不 哇噢 Lily - 女朋友?
- Slow your roll there,Lilypad. - Yeah,yeah.
- 冷静点 小Lily - 就是
You've been together all summer. I dot get it.
你们俩一个夏天都在一起 我搞不懂
Okay,it's like this.
好了 是这样的
After we kissed, we sat down to have the talk.
我们接吻后 坐下来准备谈谈
We should figure out what this is.
我们应该先弄清楚这算什么
Yes,we should. Or. Or...
是的 我们应该 又或者..
Okay,now, we have to figure this out.
好了 现在我们该弄清楚这算什么
Yes,we do. Or. Or...
是的 又或者...
We kept trying to have the talk and then we realized we hate the talk.
我们一直尝试谈心  但最终意识到我们痛恨谈那个
Yeah,the talk sucks. You have to,like,talk.
就是 谈心很讨厌 你得真的...谈心
And be all, "I don't know. "It's not that I don't like you.
类似于 "我不清楚 我不是不喜欢你
"It'sust that I haven't had a girlfriend "in a really ng time. I hope it doesn't make you mad."
"我只是很久没有女朋友了 我希望你不要生气"
- Who needs it? - You needs it.
- 谁要听这个? - 你们需要
Guys,you can't just keep hooking up and not at least try and fire out what you mean to each other.
伙计们 你们不能就这么滚床单 但完全不考虑你们对对方的意义
Yeah,we knew you would say that. That's why we kept it a secret.
我们知道你会这么说 所以才瞒着你
We,that and the fact that elaborate lies really turn us on.
这个 加上撒谎会让我们性奋
No,no,no. No.
不 不 不
You need tdefine the relationship. You ne to have the talk.
你们得界定你们的关系 得好好谈谈
Or. Or.
又或者 又或者
I know what you're all thinking.
我知道你们在想什么
"Who's this cool peer of mine up in front the class?"
"讲台前这个聪明的帅哥是谁?"
Well,I know the board says "Professor Mosby," but to you I'm Ted,huh?
我知道黑板上写的是"Mosby教授" 但你们叫我Ted就行了 明白么?
Question. Awesome. Hit it.
有人提问 棒极了 问吧
Yeah,here's my question. "Ted," who the hell do you think you are?
我的问题是 "Ted" 你以为自己是谁?
Yeah,"Ted." We're supposed to learn from you? You failed as an architect.
就是 "Ted" 我们得跟你学? 你做建筑师那么失败
Well...
呃...
And if you're a professor, where's your h and your whip?
如果你是教授 那你的帽子和鞭子呢?
They're at home.
我把它们放家里了
And where are your pants?
那你的裤子呢?
Oh,God. Barney,it was awful. I was teaching...
噢 天哪 Barney 太恐怖了 我正在上课...
Shh,Ted,now's not a good time. Whe do you keep your condoms?
嘘 Ted 我现在没空听你讲 你的安全套放哪儿了?
******
我被吓死了 我觉得我应付不来
ay,look,mistake #1 was taking that girl's question.
好吧 听着 第一个错 接受那姑娘提问
You don't ta questions on the first day. It shows weakness.
第一天不能回答问题  这只能表现你的软弱无能
Mist ake #2 was you should've hit that.
第二个错 你应该抓住机会上她
Dude,your pants were already off, u had a classroom full of people to cheer you on,
伙计 你已经脱了裤子 满教室的人会给你加油
and you n't knock her up 'cause it's a dream.
又不用担心让她怀孕 因为那是个梦
Class dismissed.
下课~
Mist ake #3,dude,where was the hat?
第三个错 伙计 那帽子呢?
Because if y're not going to wear it, I'm taking it back.
要是你不打算戴 那我就收回
I think what Barney's saying is that definitions are important.
我想Barney要说的是 界定是很重要的
You're their teacher, not their friend.
你是他们的老师 不是他们的朋友
- Exactly. - ****nobody's happy.
- 就是 - 要是不清楚各自的地位 大家都不会开心
Amen.
对极了
- You have to ma things clear. - Run tell dat.
- 应该把事情弄清楚 - 再正确不过
- Define the relationship. - Yes! No!
- 界定你们的关系 - 是啊! 不!
Lily,private convo time.
Lily 单独谈谈
Lily,can't you just let us be happy?
Lily你就不能让我们俩高高兴兴的?
You're notappy.
你们并不开心
You just think you're happy because you feel happy.
你们感到开心就以为自己真开心了
- And that's not happy? - Of course not.
- 那不是开心是什么? - 当然不是了
You and Robin need to have the talk.
你和Robin必须得谈谈
Why? Give me one good reason.
为什么? 给我个好理由先
- I'll give you 20... - Wow,you can't even think of one.
- 我可以给你20... - 哇噢 你一个理由都想不出
Headlights. Deer.
没辙了吧
Lily,for the last time, things with me and Robin are as good as they can possibly be.
Lily 我最后说一次  我跟Robin好的不能再好了
Oh,hey,look,Brad's here.
噢 嘿 瞧 Brad在那儿
I've got two tickets to the Rangers/Canucksame tomorrow night.
我有两张明晚Rangers对Canucksame的票
I know you're a hockey fan, so I was tnking...
我知道你是个冰球迷 所以我在想...
What do I have to do? Put a gun to your head?
我要怎么做才让你答应 拿枪指着你的头?
- Buy you a six ck? - Oh,come on,Brad,that's...
- 给你买六罐啤酒? - 得了吧Brad 那... (其实都是秀肌肉)
Wow,there's really six of them.
哇噢 你还真的有六块腹肌呢
- Uh,t,uh,I can't. - Why not? You have a boyfriend?
- 呃 不行 - 为什么不? 你有男朋友了?
- No. No,no boyfriend. - Great! It's a date.
- 不 没有男朋友 - 太好了! 那就这么定了
- Hey,Barn. - Hey,Br...
- 嘿 Barn - 嘿 Br...
********
我刚想到一个好理由了
***nht,Robin and Brad went to a hockey game.
第二天晚上 Robin和Brad去看冰球
You're probably wondering why I've been quiet all night.
你也许很奇怪我怎么整晚都很沉默
Damn it,Hordichuk!You miss another gimme like that,
(30秒前) 该死 Hordichuk!你要再射门失误一次
I'm gonna come down there and put a slapper right up ur beerhole! Come on!
我就跳下去狠狠爆你菊花! 快加油!
Not really.
没觉得啊
The truth is, I-I feel kind of weird being out with you.
实际上 我跟你一起出来感觉怪怪的
Oh,man. Is this the talk?
噢 我们是不是要谈谈?
- What? - No,this is od.
- 什么? - 没事 这样挺好
Let's get it all out of the way.
先把问题给解决了
Robin,I'm looking for something serious.
Robin 我想要一段认真的关系
No,Brad,no,it's...
不 Brad 不是..
But before we go any further, you should know something about my stuff below the belt.
但我们更进一步之前 你得先了解我腰带以下的一些隐秘
I was born a little different.
我天生跟别人有点不一样
God,no,uh, Brad,no,um...
老天 不 Brad 不是...
- This iabout me and Barney. - You and Barn...
- 是因为我和Barney - 你和Barney...
Oh,oh,so you, you guys are...
噢噢 所以你们俩...
Well,we-we-we don't know what we are. I mean,my heart says "leap into it."
呃 我们并不清楚我们俩算什么 我的心迫不及待要跟他在一起
My brain says "it's a bad idea."
但我的脑子说"这是个坏主意"
Sounds like you guys need to have the talk.
看来你们俩才该好好谈谈
We're not gonna have the talk!
我们才不要谈!
Would you just have the talk,okay?
你们就谈谈不行么?
It's a five-minute conversation, and then you get to have sex afterwards. It's great!
五分钟了事 然后你们就可以滚床单了 多好啊
Back me up,Ted.
帮帮我 Ted
- I don't think the talk is necessary. - What?
- 我觉得没必要谈 - 啥?
Thank you,Ted.
谢了 Ted
- Because Robin is already his girlfriend. - What?
- 因为Robin已经是他女朋友了 - 什么?
MacLaren's Bar, four years ago...
四年前 MacLaren酒吧里...
How do you keep a girl from becoming your girlfrien Simple:
如何不让姑娘们变成你的女朋友 简单:
the rules for girls are the same as the rulesfor gremlin "Gremlins"?
对付姑娘们的法子 和对付小鬼的法子一样
Gremlins.
小鬼
*******never get them wet.
第一条 永远别让他们湿身
In otherords,don't let her take a shower at your place.
换句话说 别让她在你家里洗澡
******keep them away from sunlight--
第二条 别让他们见阳光--
i.e.don't ever see them during the day.
也就是说白天不要跟她们见面
And rule # never feed them after midnight.
第三条 午夜之后千万别喂食
Meaning she doesn't sleep over and you don't have breakfast with her ever.
也就是说 她不能留宿 永远不要跟她们一起吃早餐
What about brunch? Is brunch cool?
那早午餐呢? 早午餐没问题吧?
No,Ted. unch is not cool.
不 Ted 早午餐很有问题
Ok,new topic. How do I pick a tie?
好 新话题 我如何挑选领带?
mple: remember in the movie Predator...
简单: 记得终极战士那电影吗...
I've done all three of those things with Robin.
这三件事我都跟Robin做过
Is she my girlfriend?
她真是我女朋友了?
Just once,wish you guys would call me on Tuxedo Night.
我只想说 真希望你们俩 燕尾服之夜时会叫上我
Ladies and gentlemen, time to pucker up for the New York Rangers Kiss Cam!
女士们先生们  又到了纽约游骑兵队屏幕热吻时间!
Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss! Kiss!
快亲! 快亲! 快亲!
Okayhow about this?
这么办怎么样?
If you kiss me and you feel bad about it, you're meant to be with Barney.
如果你亲了我 然后心存不安 那你就应该跟Barney在一起
Why not? Lay it on me.
为什么不? 来吧
Kiss!
快亲!
Hey,Bd.
嘿 Brad
Brad,we can't fight like this all night!
Brad 我们不能这么一直打下去!
We both got some good shots in. Let's call a truce!
我们各有胜负 让我们休战吧!
It's oy,dude.
没事的 伙计
I shouldn't go kissing some other guy's girlfriend.
是我不应该亲吻别人的女朋友
Whoa,whoa,whoa, whoa,girlfriend? He come on.
喔喔喔 什么女朋友呀? 得了吧
- That's putting it a bit strongly. - A bit strongly. She's no *******
- 你这就言重了 - 言重咯 她才不是我的女朋友
A gifriend's a bit much,Brad,okay?
说是女朋友就太过啦 Brad 对吧?
Okay,seriously. We're at the point of physical violence.
好吧 说真的 都演变成暴力事件啦
Now,will you ease have the talk?
这下 你们该好好谈谈了吧?
Because of that? Come on. That's thing.
就为了这个? 拜托哦 打架是家常便饭呀
I'm always punching guys.
我一直打人的
Girls-- I'll punch a baby. I don't care.
还是打女人吧 随便了 打小孩也无所谓
Finally,my first clas had arrived. For real this time.
终于 我开始了我的第一堂课  这次是真的了
I knew I had to make a strong iression.
我明白我得留下个好印象
I had thought of everything. Except...
我已经考虑周详 除了...
Wait. Does professor have one "F" or two? Oh,my God. Oh,my God.
等下 教授该怎么拼啊? 一个F还是两个? 苍天啊苍天
Professor. Pro-fess-or. They're all starg at me.
教授...教授 他们都盯着我
Professor. Uh,I don't know. Ju do something!
教授 嗯 我不知道 随便了!
Two "F's." That looks right. I think that's right.
两个F 看上去蛮对的 我觉得蛮对的
Hey,sorry I went little too far last night.
对不起哦 我昨晚做的太过了
Oh,look,we've been over this. Unless I say "fl gelhorn," you haven't gone too far.
听着 我们都明白的  除非我说"夫吕号" 你都没做错啥 （夫吕号:一种乐器）
No,meant punching Brad.
不是的 我是说打Brad的事
Oh,right. Look, don't even worry about it. It's...
没事的 听着 根本不用担心这个 这是...
God. The doorknob's broken off. We're locked in here.
天哪 门栓掉下来了 我们被锁在里面了
Did,did you do this?
是 是你干的么?
- No. - Fl gelhorn. Did you do this?
- 不是 - 夫吕号 是你干的不?
No.
不是
Ted? Ted,are you out there?
Ted? Ted 是你在外面吗?
Ted's not here,Robin.
Ted不在 Robin
Lily,let us out of here.
Lily 放我们出去
I'd be glad to.
我很乐意这样做
Just as soon as you and Barney have the talk.
只要你和Barney肯谈谈
Lily! Co on. Let us out!
Lily! 拜托了 让我们出去!
No. Sit down, define the relationship, write down that definition on a piece of paper,
不行 你们给我坐下 界定你们的关系 然后把这个定义写在纸上
slip it under the door, and if I like what I read, you can go.
从门缝里送出来  如果我满意了 你们就可以出来了
We are not having the talk!
我们才不要谈!
Then you'll die in there.
那你们就老死在里面吧
You're gonna lock us in here? Well,guess what?
你想把我们锁在这里? 你猜怎么着?
Maybe we'll spend the whole day having sex!
我们就嘿咻一天!
Well,guess at?
你猜怎么着?
I brought Marshall with me, so maybe we'll do the same.
我把Marshall也带来了  我们也能如法炮制
Hey,guys.
你们好
I stilhadn't decided what kind of professor I wanted to be-- authoritative or cool guy.
我依然无法决定我要成为怎样的教授 威严的或是酷酷的
I thought I would decide in the moment.
我以为我马上就能决定
**********
而事实上 我决定了大概20多次
Goodorning. 'Sup,dudes? Silence!
早上好 怎么样啊 伙计们? 给我安静!
This is Architecture 101. I am Professor Mosby.
这是建筑学101课 我是Mosby教授
But you can call me Ted.
你也可以叫我Ted
Professor Mosby. T-Dawg.
还是Mosby教授吧 或者是小白脸
Do not call me T-Dawg.
不许叫我小白脸!
Ner take questions on the first day. It shows weakness.
第一天不能回答问题  这只能表现你的软弱无能
Also, don't look right here.
也不要盯着这里看
Okay,good luck. Byesies.
好运哦 我闪了
This was it: my crossroads moment.
终于来了 我做抉择的时刻到了
What kind of professor was I gonna be I had to decide.
我到底要成为怎样的教授 我必须决定了
Please save all your qstions until the end of the lecture. Thank you! Now...
等课结束再问问题吧 谢谢咯!  现在...
Professor Mosby d arrived.
Mosby教授诞生了
Of course,if I had taken that girl's question--
当然 如果我让那个女孩问问题的话
who,by the way,was not your mo Your mom was sitting...
说一下 她不是你们的妈妈 你们的妈妈坐在...
Wait,let me finish this story al quick.
算了 还是让我快点讲完吧
Here's what that girl wod have said.
以下是这个女孩本来要说的话
I'm sorry to bother you,Professor Mo but this isn't Architecture 101.
不好意思 Mosby教授  但这不是建筑学101
This is Economics 305.
这里是经济学305
You're in the wrong classroom.
你走错教室了哦
Yes,I was in the wrong classroom.
没错 我走错教室了
And thus began the most humiliating ven minutesof my life.
于是我人生中的黑色七分钟开始了
Here's your ink-about-it for the day.
你们应该好好想想
Every single person in this room is already an architect.
每个在这个教室里的人 都已经是一个建筑师
Architt?
建筑师?
"We're just hanging out."
"我们只是一起玩玩"
Just hanging out?
一起玩玩?
- Not good enough. - Not good enough!
- 不怎么样 - 不怎么样!
Can anyone here tell me what this class is really all about?
有没有人能够告诉我  这堂课的主旨究竟是什么?
Economics?
经济?
No. No,no. Don't ugh. He's not... He's not entirely wrong.
不不不 不要笑 他... 他也不算完全错
An architect must be economical in his use of space,
建筑师必须经济合理地运用空间
so,well done.
说的不错
Looks like somne's building towards an A,huh?
看来有人可以得A咯?
"We're seeing where things are going."
"我们静待事态发展"
I'll tell you where things aren't ing-- out of that bedroom.
我来告诉你们 事态不会怎么发展 你们就一直呆在房间里面吧
- Not good enough. - Not good eugh!
- 不怎么样 - 不怎么样!
You-- why do you want to be an architect?
你 你说说为什么要成为建筑师?
I don't want to be an architect.
我不想成为建筑师
Yes. Yes,exactly.
没错 非常正确
It-It's not something you want to be.
不是你想成为
It's something you need to be.
而且你必须要成为
You dot have a choice,right?
你们别无选择 对不对?
None of you has a choice. No questions!
你们都无从选择 不许问问题!
"We're Barnman and Robin."
"我们是巴尼侠和罗宾" (模仿蝙蝠侠和罗宾)
Oh,come on,you got to admit, that's kind of fun,Lily.
算了啦 你得承认 这个还是蛮好笑的 Lily
Not good enough.
不怎么样
Not good enough!
不怎么样!
So if any of you have even the slightest inclination to do anything with your life
如果你们的人生 除了建筑以外
other than become an archite,
还有别的什么爱好
you're wasting my time and yours.
你在浪费你我的时间
There's the door You can go.
那边有门 你们尽管可以离开
*******
我说真的 滚出去 滚出去
Wait,wait,wait. Don't-Don't all leave!
等下等下 别都走呀!
Architecture's fun! Look! I brought a hacky sack!
建筑很好玩的 看呀! 我还买了个踢包! (一种游戏 类似于沙包)
SorrI'm late,everyone.
对不起 各位 我迟到了
My name is Professor Calzonetti. This is Economics 305.
我是Calzonetti教授 这里是经济学305
You may return to your seats.
请回到自己的座位上
Uh,sorry,sir. This is,uh,Architecture 101.
对不起 先生 这里是建筑学101
Who invited their dad,right?
谁把自己老爸也带来啦?
Young man, for the last 28 years,
年轻人 28年以来 经济学305
Economics 305 has been taught right here inuilding 14,room 7.
都在这里 也就是14楼7教室授课
Uh,yeah.
没错
Buddy,I'm sure 200 architecture students antheir professor all got the room wrong.
伙计 难道是200名建筑学学生 和他们的教授都走错教室了?
T-Dawg, you're in the wrong room,bro.
小白脸 只有你走错教室了
****** Sorry. Comg through.
让开 对不起 借过借过
Excuse me.
不好意思
20 minutes late on your first day?
第一堂课就迟到了20分钟?
That's rough.
太惨了
Yeah,but here's the funny thing.
没错 但有意思的是
By that point, I didn't have time to think about what kind of teacher I was going to be.
正因如此 我没有时间去考虑 我要成为怎样的教授
I just got up there and talked about architecture.
我只是赶到那里 开始谈论建筑
And it was kind of great.
还挺不错的
- That's awesome,Ted. - Yeah. Congratulations,buddy.
- 真不错 Ted - 恭喜你 兄弟
- Thanks. - Nice job,Ted.
- 谢谢 - 干得好 Ted
Hey,Ted,door five!
嘿 Ted 来个门上击掌!
- Were you there? - Yeah,I got you, buddy.
- 在么? - 我击到了 兄弟
They still haven't had the talk,huh?
他们还是不肯谈?
I think I know how to speed things up
我知道怎么能快一点
Oh,not cool!
你们太恶劣了!
Pancakes,fresh bacon.
薄煎饼 新鲜培根
It is so yummy.
太好吃了
Uh,dude, I'm starving. Let's...
伙计 我快饿死了 我们...
Let's just have the stupid talk. Come on.
我们就谈谈这愚蠢的事情吧 快点
Fine.
好吧
But how do these this even work? What do we say?
怎么谈呀 我们该谈什么?
********
你们觉得这段感情将如何发展
Oh,my God, that sounds so cheesy.
苍天啊 听上去好肉麻
- I know,right? - Totally.
- 说的对 - 就是
But,um, where-where do you see this relationship going?
但是 你觉得这段感情会如何发展?
I don't know.
我不知道
I mean, it's not like I don't like you.
我是说 我不是不喜欢你
I just haven't had a girlfriend for a long time.
我只是很久没有女朋友了
I hope that doesn't make you mad.
我希望你不要生气
Mad? I feel the same way. I suck at relationshs.
生气? 我也这么想 我根本谈不好恋爱
I mean, exceptith Ted.
除了Ted
Man,he really got it right.
他的确是很合适我
I know it's a clich? but he really ruined me for other men.
我知道这很老套?  但是他的确让我无法再接受别的男人
Of course,I wasn't in the room for this conversation,
我当然不在房间里 听不到这段对话
but I have to imagine bin said something like that.
不过我也能猜到 Robin一定说了这样的话
Maybe we should go back to being jt friends.
也许我们该做回朋友
Maybe.
也许吧
But,um, I don't want to stop having sex.
不过 我不想停止嘿咻
Oh,good. Me,neither.
太好了 我也不想
- Yeah. Friends isn't gonna work. - Nope.
- 只做朋友不行 - 没错
Oh,we're not good at being friends. We're nogood at being in a relationship. Wh are we good at?
我们不擅长做朋友 不擅长谈恋爱  那我们擅长什么呢?
I know something we're good at.
我知道我们擅长什么
I don't know. If we're gonna do it again, I'm gonna need some Gatorade,or...
不好说啊 如果再"做"的话  我恐怕要喝点佳得乐解渴了 (解口渴更解体渴)
No! No,t that. Lying.
不是的 不是说那个 我说的是撒谎
Oy,think about it. We spent the whole summer lying about being just friends.
想想看 我们撒了一个夏天的谎了  说我们只是朋友
Why not just keep lying?
为什么不继续说谎呢?
- Really? - Yeah. Really.
- 真的? - 没错 是真的
We sat down. We had the talk.
我们坐下了 好好谈了
- Barney's my boyfriend now. - And Robin's myirlfriend.
- Barney现在是我的男朋友了 - Robin是我的女朋友了
I know it sounds nuts, but it feels good to say.
我知道听上去很疯狂  但是这么说感觉真好
We're both afraid ofommitment, but,the fact is, we also can't live without each other.
我们都害怕承诺 但是事实是  我们都离不开对方
And if the alternative is not being together, then it's worth taking this risk 'cause...
如果非要我们分开  我们愿意去尝试冒险 因为...
she's awesome.
她很棒
And he's awesome. He lks nice in a suit.
他也很棒 他穿西装很帅
She n handle her Scotch.
她挺能喝的
He's my boyfriend.
他是我的男朋友
And she's my girlfriend.
她是我的女朋友
Good enough!
说得好!
She bought it.
她上当啦
Hook,line,and sinker. are good.
成功上钩 我们真行
Oh,totally.
说的没错
So,yowant to get some breakfast?
想去吃早餐吗?
You know,brunch actuall does sound kind of good.
早午餐听上去也不错
Well,lead the way, sweetie pie.
带路吧 心肝宝贝
Wh! Fl gelhorn.
喔 夫吕号 (受不了的甜蜜啊)
Yeah,that felt wrong.
对 感觉好怪哦
You do realize they were lying,right?
你明白他们在撒谎吧?
No,Ted. ey don't realize they weren't lying.
不对 Ted 是他们不明白他们没有撒谎
*******
真是疯了
Oh,hello. Hello. Good evening. Hello. Don't get up.
好啊 你好 晚上好 噢 别站起来
Didn't we meet on a yacht? Hello.
我们是不是在游艇上见过? 你好
- What? - Oh,no!
- 干嘛? - 噢 不好!
Did I not tell you guys that it was Tuxedo Night?
我没有和你们说今天是燕尾服之夜吗?
Doesn't feel very good,does it?
很难过吧 对不对?
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=- proudly presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- 荣誉出品  本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径